{"data":{"createNewExamAttempt":{"attempt":{"id":"0c2d0527-456b-404c-87ee-91cedaf03720"},"exam":{"id":"c452045c-5d95-4429-a430-1b22ed3fea15","title":"AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Exam","duration":5400,"totalQuestions":65,"questions":[{"id":"7i7znw7n-wyau-1p97-x0mw-czmau22hc7od","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following is not part of the AWS Global infrastructure?","explanation":"Regions, AZs, and Edge Locations are part of the AWS Global Infrastructure. Security Groups are a part of IAM (Identity and Access Management)","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"17d8fc1e4ceb765476776889d7f6c5ab","text":"Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"1fb6aae6611aa5001c41c1e356609c41","text":"Availability Zones","correct":false},{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":true},{"id":"5948f3347ebc02ebc690227c059661e1","text":"Regions","correct":false}]},{"id":"4rfhb5p7-g8iu-y8mp-p4pm-w5dpyvxtin9c","domain":"tech","question":"You want to run your application on a PaaS infrastructure, and you need to be able to select both your instance type and your database. Which of the following services should you choose?","explanation":"Elastic Beanstalk will allow you to select both your instance type and your database type. EC2 is considered Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS) and not Platform as a service. With Lambda and Lightsail you do not have the ability to select you instance type","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/elasticbeanstalk/","title":"About Elastic Beanstalk"}],"answers":[{"id":"04a7da3c5b04cad85da1eebb92315b8b","text":"Lambda","correct":false},{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false},{"id":"b21eea42e76007ac061cf37a5a41037d","text":"Lightsail","correct":false},{"id":"3d6cbd7db2a4fa389808ea6f4a5fc1bc","text":"Elastic Beanstalk","correct":true}]},{"id":"cf545dc9-39ca-4eec-869f-0d416b59aa1f","domain":"concepts","question":"Adding resources to your application as user demand grows is an example of which cloud concept?","explanation":"Scalability is the concept that as cloud has essentially limitless capacity, it allows you to expand out as needed - as detailed in the question. Automation relates to simplyfying common repeated tasks and removing the human element. Although elasticity (the ability to go up and down in resources as needed) is related, this question specifically ask for in in response to user demand, which is closer to Scalability. High Availability relates to the ability of your application to withstand failures in Cloud Infrastructure.","links":[],"answers":[{"id":"caea8340e2d186a540518d08602aa065","text":"Automation","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":true},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false},{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":false}]},{"id":"3f2cee98-aedc-43ec-a5f6-2de9a48a9885","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following engines are classified as relational databases on AWS?","explanation":"Aurora and MariaDB are two types of RDS engines on AWS. Redshift is for data warehousing, and DynamoDB is Amazon’s non-relational database solution.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/","title":"Amazon Relational Database Service (RDS)"}],"answers":[{"id":"509e0895bd82e3315e79018a6ce02181","text":"Aurora","correct":true},{"id":"7f9733e208088b1ce6df3d4be1765396","text":"MariaDB","correct":true},{"id":"6ebb7423072c5943f52c11274fd71b0b","text":"DynamoDB","correct":false},{"id":"f52a9d91766886fb3a524dd06d1581cb","text":"Redshift","correct":false}]},{"id":"eaf197bf-a9f1-4611-90be-dbcf7364c74a","domain":"concepts","question":"You have an application load balancer for routing traffic from developers to the EC2 instance that contains a web application being put into operation. To prepare for the application going live for public use, you add an Auto Scaling Group and a second application load balancer to route web traffic from customers to the EC2 instance. The addition is an example of which of the following:","explanation":"This is an example of scalability, which means that systems are expected to grow over time with no drop in performance. ","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"2166e76dc88d642260416a536b06a412","text":"Durability","correct":false},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":true},{"id":"820b8f74ad843d1574106ec4cadfc07e","text":"Reliability","correct":false}]},{"id":"7a194fa6-5966-4548-9b32-ac602a517ac8","domain":"concepts","question":"With AWS services, you can use as many resources as you need, as well as use them when you need them. Which of the following terms can be applied to this concept?","explanation":"Working in a traditional infrastructure environment means that you have to deal with fixed resources, which is comparatively costly and labor-intensive. By contrast, AWS services are much more convenient; the services provide the ability to use as many resources as you need and dispose of them when you no longer need them. That’s why such resources are both temporary and disposable.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"5936fc4450b6f3f75cc6fe08d2890b77","text":"Temporary resources","correct":true},{"id":"e035a6f9ed7c8c3c99e48b95e32cc364","text":"Fixed resources","correct":false},{"id":"83ec702ebd8e13f87318dba136356773","text":"Dedicated resources","correct":false},{"id":"fd3ca13906a4c1e05f791d27dbc66914","text":"Disposable resources","correct":true}]},{"id":"2o4xzter-rc6s-wz14-cd0x-5ymcmahyoj0q","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are you responsible for when running an EC2 instance on AWS?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model, EC2 patching is a Shared Control - AWS is responsible for the underlying hardware, but you as the user is responsible for patching the OS and Applications running in your instance","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"92d4ae83f773c1e79ec7ae29b20fa481","text":"Patching the network hardware","correct":false},{"id":"ce74e3a1c22bccb58acc0062f43153bd","text":"Patching the compute hardware","correct":false},{"id":"3e164c265c82649647e641e322d93aa7","text":"Patching the operating system","correct":true},{"id":"b8a5da87a2cdeca59f9782e25182f574","text":"Patching the applications","correct":true}]},{"id":"5a168390-1f66-11ea-a5e8-2e728ce88125","domain":"security","question":"You added a recently hired HR Assistant to the IAM group named 'HumanResources'. Which of the following statements will apply to that user?","explanation":"By adding the HR Assistant to the 'HumanResources' group by using the AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) service, the new hiree is now a member of the company’s HR department and inherits the administrative permissions of that group.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/getting-started_create-admin-group.html","title":"Create Your First IAM Admin User and Group"}],"answers":[{"id":"4f98907d2b5e12fad173f30f4d61ec84","text":"The HR Assistant inherits the permissions of the 'HumanResources' group.","correct":true},{"id":"a445a3cad5d84550114916ae6df763c4","text":"The HR Assistant becomes leader of the Human Resources department.","correct":false},{"id":"b098a137cb3a11528e46deb8c5aff98d","text":"The HR Assistant becomes an IAM member of the company’s Human Resources department.","correct":true},{"id":"367051fc494f2dba53682af0d5f9a9e1","text":"The HR Assistant becomes the AWS root account user.","correct":false}]},{"id":"upv9n2ts-iwzj-4vez-gyls-rnpppswzz8zm","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below is true about root accounts on AWS?","explanation":"The root user has access to absolutely everything in an AWS account, and therefore should not be used for normal day to day activities and be reserved for when things go wrong. AWS will never ask you for any usernames or passwords as part of a support request  - so any request to do so should be treated with suspicion. The root user cannot be disabled.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_root-user.html","title":"The AWS Root User"}],"answers":[{"id":"547527745e6b2e9620cf7400b9c03c91","text":"The root user has full access to everything in the AWS account","correct":true},{"id":"5c25f0724b86a34c79909772ae00ddd2","text":"The root user should be disabled after you create an Admin user","correct":false},{"id":"3db3937d9b6115b761fee0d0a7ad9975","text":"The root user is the recommended way to work in the AWS Console","correct":false},{"id":"eb189b7195d97fe576a8babd440bd471","text":"The root user should not be used for day to day activities","correct":true},{"id":"8d2e8228cfcd751c2f8d90fe0712a9f0","text":"The root user will be used by AWS should they need to help you with something in your account","correct":false}]},{"id":"1cfba8e0-0fb8-11ea-8d71-362b9e155667","domain":"billing","question":"You have EC2 and RDS instances, Redshift and Elasticsearch clusters, and an SNS topic in your AWS environment. Which of these services support reserved pricing?","explanation":"Amazon SNS is the only one of the five mentioned services that does not have reserved pricing. On the other hand, Amazon EC2, RDS, Redshift, and Elasticsearch do.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 Pricing"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/pricing/","title":"Amazon RDS Pricing"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/redshift/pricing/","title":"Amazon Redshift Pricing"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/elasticsearch-service/pricing/","title":"Amazon Elasticsearch Service Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"fcb02ff285a97f0ed386c6cfe36b02f4","text":"EC2, RDS, Redshift, and Elasticsearch","correct":true},{"id":"0221d4f5950f35dfcf98f6a60f60d20d","text":" Elasticsearch and SNS","correct":false},{"id":"3ec389f2e16e0e0443f3ef49d2b58d05","text":"EC2 and RDS","correct":false},{"id":"65e4dd05e0a1392e55661f27717e96cb","text":"RDS, Redshift, Elasticsearch, and SNS","correct":false},{"id":"9d6fbf729ccc02278cc50176a91ed3fe","text":"EC2, Redshift, and SNS","correct":false}]},{"id":"rc4dwp79-ix5s-h912-sdcj-9gmmhl6zacte","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following is AWS' managed DDoS protection service?","explanation":"AWS Shield is AWS' managed DDoS protection service at Layer 4. AWS WAF provides protection from common exploits against your web applications at Layer 7, and does not protect against DDoS attacks.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/shield/?nc2=h_l3_dm","title":"About AWS Shield"}],"answers":[{"id":"303a25c2935ec1fdb01208b6f4f65688","text":"Access Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"32685c9f0403b41381bf5f88788ad995","text":"AWS WAF","correct":false},{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":false},{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":true}]},{"id":"smnrxkfv-dk56-snvh-i93e-or0vfomvccbz","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are characteristics of cloud computing?","explanation":"The on-demand delivery via the internet of services with pay-as-you-go pricing characterizes cloud computing. Services incurred from a cloud services provider are operating expenses, not capital expenses. Capital Expenditure (CAPEX) is less common with the cloud, in favour of Operational Expenditure (OPEX). Skills and training for personnel are required to leverage Cloud Computing","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/what-is-cloud-computing/","title":"What is Cloud Computing?"}],"answers":[{"id":"2b34d3fef0b313e0047a2557d9842378","text":"Pay-as-you-go pricing","correct":true},{"id":"481f1c72f1007c1ac8e4a484b47af4f2","text":"Cloud charges are Capital Expenditures.","correct":false},{"id":"9b670633c5238ca5a17dd651c3a63662","text":"No extra skills or training are required.","correct":false},{"id":"ebc744edbd870e96fe9e680b407ad053","text":"On-demand delivery","correct":true},{"id":"dcfe379beaf88dbe9d59e7fcecf6f98a","text":"Services are delivered via the Internet.","correct":true}]},{"id":"8r7r7n13-hvyw-63f9-gltg-21wwwmux0grq","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following best describes a system that will remain operational even in the event of a component failure?","explanation":"a fault-tolerant system will remain operational even in the event of a component failure.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/whitepapers/designing-fault-tolerant-applications/","title":"Building Fault-Tolerant Applications in the AWS Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"a078ed5ade8df4aac54efbdb57e63ad2","text":"Elastic","correct":false},{"id":"7bf4251c070de07f503b12b9d341daea","text":"Fault-tolerant","correct":true},{"id":"28cb2468ce3a85b4d10668ec48f5e4d6","text":"Scalable","correct":false},{"id":"9818cb0bfa2dfb200a8c078b1fe1c2fd","text":"Highly Available","correct":false}]},{"id":"2cp5w12s-zexu-46ts-0im3-vuthjxgjujs3","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following best describes the ability to scale computing resources up or down easily, while only paying for the resources used?","explanation":"Elasticity describes the ability to scale computing resources up or down easily, while only paying for the resources used.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for The Cloud: Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":false},{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":false},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":true},{"id":"fb76c61f626c7fb0fd2ee1226e9fd8bd","text":"Fault-tolerance","correct":false}]},{"id":"q9rl4dzm-8wyq-y23f-41wx-15rhrz976akb","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are a collection of datacentres within a specific region?","explanation":"Availability Zones are a collection of datacentres within a specific region.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"5948f3347ebc02ebc690227c059661e1","text":"Regions","correct":false},{"id":"1fb6aae6611aa5001c41c1e356609c41","text":"Availability Zones","correct":true},{"id":"2bdbf4724b81ff0529e32fdb1af28130","text":"AWS Origins","correct":false},{"id":"17d8fc1e4ceb765476776889d7f6c5ab","text":"Edge Locations","correct":false}]},{"id":"95gxdl84-1tio-ykg7-co3h-3zwy6zgp5w46","domain":"tech","question":"For which of the following categories does AWS Trusted Advisor provides best practices and/or or checks of your AWS environment?","explanation":"Trusted Advisor provides best practices and/or or checks on Cost Optimization, Performance, Security, and Fault Tolerance.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/trustedadvisor/features/","title":"Trusted Advisor - Features"}],"answers":[{"id":"9505247cbbe2382d170a963c34412544","text":"High-Availability","correct":false},{"id":"1aeb2b2616be71f57f6f9f4252b8b4f5","text":"Availability of AWS resources","correct":false},{"id":"d0bf6ab153eaa104c878925472ff129a","text":"Cost Optimization","correct":true},{"id":"2fae32629d4ef4fc6341f1751b405e45","text":"Security","correct":true},{"id":"9446a98ad14416153cc4d45ab8b531bf","text":"Performance","correct":true},{"id":"731f2cc67a37d0506652a949cc568a24","text":"Right-size","correct":false},{"id":"aa18abedec09bd4f85e612c307e2eaa6","text":"Fault Tolerance","correct":true}]},{"id":"t9dm8phv-f52w-bfsh-qrp9-6p8yl3d9o992","domain":"tech","question":"For a subnet to be public and send non-local traffic to the Internet, we must update the Route Table of the public subnet and attach which of the following to the VPC that contains the subnet?","explanation":"An Internet Gateway enables resources inside you VPC to reach the internet, as long as route tables and IP addresses are correctly configured in your environment.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonVPC/latest/UserGuide/VPC_Internet_Gateway.html","title":"About Internet Gateways"}],"answers":[{"id":"3fdc04800c36e2177d81c4431616f533","text":"Internet Gateway","correct":true},{"id":"8ca0f1328403ec0d05ed995272d74715","text":"NAT Gateway","correct":false},{"id":"c8525a9dfff01ff2bc0d471627bc0708","text":"Network Access Control List","correct":false},{"id":"0893147538c21c827dc499b4852934e3","text":"Route 53","correct":false}]},{"id":"5ca8852d-519a-409a-b998-d74eb78ef5cf","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are Amazon EFS (Elastic File Storage) storage classes?","explanation":"There are two Amazon EFS storage classes, which are Standard and Infrequent Access. One Zone – Infrequent Access, Intelligent Tiering, and Deep Glacier are names specifically for Amazon S3 storage classes.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/efs/latest/ug/whatisefs.html","title":"What Is Amazon Elastic File System?"}],"answers":[{"id":"13c28d56109c12a096b5e325b65a1c01","text":"Intelligent Tiering","correct":false},{"id":"9f0832b6670166f059cfdc8dc49133b4","text":"One Zone - Infrequent Access","correct":false},{"id":"eb6d8ae6f20283755b339c0dc273988b","text":"Standard","correct":true},{"id":"72156eca90dac061dfd0a6da22c5e9b0","text":"Deep Glacier","correct":false},{"id":"b1926a8ac417114ef193a282594538c7","text":"Infrequent Access","correct":true}]},{"id":"6sole68h-iivl-m9l8-zztc-bfdk38rdagvy","domain":"security","question":"In which order is a user granted access to AWS services?","explanation":"The user is Authenticated, then Authorized to use AWS services.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/iam/details/","title":"About IAM"}],"answers":[{"id":"a6a56d56f380bafb99d9c83d0ea32240","text":"The user is Authenticated, then Authorized to use AWS services.","correct":true},{"id":"0d3c25cb8fbf51013a4258262d14a6ff","text":"The user is Authorized, then Authenticated.","correct":false}]},{"id":"e3b24121-862f-4b1e-8f4e-18e6f3f9e1e8","domain":"concepts","question":"VMware Cloud on AWS allows companies to migrate and extend their on-premises VMware vSphere-based environments to AWS Cloud using Amazon EC2. Which of the following choices accurately classifies this deployment model?","explanation":"Hybrid deployments connect infrastructure and applications between cloud-based resources and existing resources that are not located in the cloud. VMware Cloud on AWS is an example of a hybrid deployment, since it involves the on-premises environments of VMware and the cloud-based services of AWS.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/hybrid/","title":"Hybrid Cloud with AWS"}],"answers":[{"id":"d6eb128e4c8971dc397f021585391999","text":"Shared Services","correct":false},{"id":"0fca8d17afc46bb08bd2d70a26cdf886","text":"On-Premises","correct":false},{"id":"c8e2277ecfb1427838c488c217f99466","text":"Cloud","correct":false},{"id":"fb1b6e23a3767d2a31ef7899e6dd3f1e","text":"Hybrid","correct":true}]},{"id":"71sehgn8-lx4k-034j-srs9-vv6xhd7w10qh","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are principles of sound design when it comes to performance efficiency?","explanation":"Of these choices, you should democratize advanced technologies, deploy into multiple Regions, and use Serverless technologies.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for The Cloud: Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"8c3a4b8048462b1877e2da598308fe3a","text":"Democratize advanced technologies.","correct":true},{"id":"56110ec02fe5d9a3ae8e5a69af838158","text":"Have your IT staff master all new technologies.","correct":false},{"id":"e891a453952de1898dde71f36801790a","text":"Use Serverless architectures.","correct":true},{"id":"c25dea02447eef08ddb2affdbb171485","text":"Mechanical empathy","correct":false},{"id":"db3e408a0aa09a4e83bdace8a1e57fcc","text":"Deploy into multiple Regions to go global in minutes.","correct":true}]},{"id":"porkjt4t-1idl-7vgv-mx2b-s6gvayouwvh4","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are advantages of cloud computing?","explanation":"Elasticity, Agility, and the ability to control the variances in your month-to-month expenditure are all advantages of the flexibility of Cloud Computing. You do still need specialist knowledge to deploy solutions in the Cloud, such as AWS Certifications. Large amounts of capital are also not needed due to the consumption model of most cloud services, although you can sometimes use capital expenditure to purchase resources for extended periods of time, such as Reserved Instances in EC2.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/what-is-cloud-computing/","title":"What is Cloud Computing?"}],"answers":[{"id":"97e11cb086bf1070777e7e3fa1e31877","text":"Requires large amounts of capital","correct":false},{"id":"230dee0a7da58ba8fbf9dee4e7448de2","text":"Elasticity - you need not worry about capacity.","correct":true},{"id":"a0368a69e2586f302d0f3da6bfa3b031","text":"Agility - Decreasing the time to start new services","correct":true},{"id":"e614fc350d8c3730eaca43265d43d9de","text":"Variable expense","correct":true},{"id":"b6244c70b8f2eb23f7eb82a740202646","text":"No specialist knowledge required","correct":false}]},{"id":"prqyybkg-4flz-vdjf-hmny-u1q34ck87hm9","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are AWS compute services?","explanation":"EC2 and Lambda are AWS Compute Services, while RDS is a Database service, and SNS is an Application Integration service.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/products/compute/","title":"AWS Compute"}],"answers":[{"id":"54afc4697cf03d8e3ec9a05b16380622","text":"SNS","correct":false},{"id":"0f41d6f36f8eaee87ea08d9f4b1159e2","text":"RDS","correct":false},{"id":"04a7da3c5b04cad85da1eebb92315b8b","text":"Lambda","correct":true},{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":true}]},{"id":"2cae08d8-1bce-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following types of data transfer concerning Amazon EC2 are free?","explanation":"All data transfer in to EC2 instances from the Internet is free. So is data transfer out of EC2 to CloudFront. Data transfer pricing out from EC2 to the Internet is free as long as it does not exceed 1 GB per month. Since this condition is not included in Response B, it isn’t correct.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/on-demand/#Data_Transfer","title":"EC2 Instance Pricing – Data Transfer"}],"answers":[{"id":"9a1bfe89c1c91cf60b45ef77bf406e09","text":"Data transfer out from EC2 to Amazon CloudFront","correct":true},{"id":"2f08e8cef2078b8c6479a4b91faeeec3","text":"Data transfer in to EC2 from the Internet","correct":true},{"id":"279a4b71d3edd9b515bb71952e1a12c7","text":"Data transfer out from EC2 to AWS GovCloud","correct":false},{"id":"3b4e686ed0886b7be7e142139c38eb68","text":"Data transfer out from EC2 to the Internet","correct":false}]},{"id":"0b2dkrmk-derf-tm5u-h127-w4yffwtldij2","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following are Support Levels offered by AWS?","explanation":"AWS Support has four levels. Basic is their free entitlement for all AWS Customers. The three paid support plans in order of ascending cost are Developer, Business, and Enterprise. Start-up and Individual do not exist as Support Plans","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"2dd4472245a696bc0b4b944db2a8b519","text":"Individual","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":true},{"id":"3263b7364a2b2cb3d4697003ef512748","text":"Start-up","correct":false},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":true}]},{"id":"a1113592-8add-4bc5-bc72-07b4af069ecb","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following enables customers to find, test, and buy software from independent vendors to run on AWS?","explanation":"AWS Marketplace is the place to get software that runs on AWS. Amazon Connect is a cloud-based contact center; AWS Cost Explorer is for evaluating your account costs and usage, and AWS Budgets is for budgeting costs and usage.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/marketplace","title":"AWS Marketplace"}],"answers":[{"id":"cab27dc53edb571cac663ce2e16450dc","text":"AWS Marketplace","correct":true},{"id":"3597dfc4f30310d82a68c84b2c82e1a8","text":"Amazon Connect","correct":false},{"id":"c7f176d72688fd87853e31b84159d541","text":"AWS Cost Explorer","correct":false},{"id":"e32a801c8e0beab6abb9361e937365be","text":"AWS Budgets","correct":false}]},{"id":"0mdd9dnl-ji3o-hjum-lyr4-wtpoks65v0z9","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following statements about AWS Region is true?","explanation":"A region is a geographical area divided into Availability Zones. Each region contains at least two publicly accessible Availability Zones.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"bec481a5e2c63bfc93d4922d5845bd2b","text":"Regions are only available in some locations globally","correct":false},{"id":"2cf30d8c571fe080cdd53d0a78db5689","text":"Regions are automatically fully synchronized to contain the same data globally","correct":false},{"id":"1c52cae4b07ea355b6bf0d1522efc7e7","text":"Regions are made up of Availability Zones","correct":true},{"id":"fddc13d769887bc62fc14c8d844e1aa9","text":"Regions are generally specific geographical areas","correct":true}]},{"id":"bccfe3b0-61d9-4680-81cc-45a78d8a722d","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following options are available for configuring a password policy for IAM users of an AWS account?","explanation":"The password policy options does not include the requirement of using at least one numerical character from 1 to 9; it is actually at least one numerical character from 0 to 9. Passwords can contain between 6 to 128 characters, so 12 to 64 characters is incorrect. The other three options listed are correct.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_credentials_passwords_account-policy.html?icmpid=docs_iam_console","title":"Setting an Account Password Policy for IAM Users"}],"answers":[{"id":"454e4156bef76a1758de1fb18c771f5b","text":"Require that passwords contain at least one of the AWS-listed nonalphanumeric characters.","correct":true},{"id":"164affd52e9cf98d09976ffa798d82dd","text":"Allow users to change their passwords.","correct":true},{"id":"fcce064756de55a96a60925043d2feb0","text":"Use between 12 to 64 characters to form the password.","correct":false},{"id":"9fd02d6b80fbf23454be435b3ecbe598","text":"Use between 6 to 128 characters to form the password.","correct":true},{"id":"7115f92e53f08f3e583dcfde0a88161b","text":"Use at least one numerical character from 1 to 9.","correct":false}]},{"id":"4885465a-c1a0-41e2-8e7d-d6ac27557522","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following comprises an Amazon Machine Image (AMI)?","explanation":"An AMI includes three types of information. There’s the Amazon EBS snapshot or snapshots for backing up EBS volume data to S3, or a template for the root volume of the instance if the AMI is instance-store-backed. There are launch permissions for controlling which AWS accounts can use the AMI to launch an instance. And there’s block device mapping for specifying the volumes to attach to the instance when it’s launched. These are the pieces of information that AMI requires to launch an EC2 instance; the EC2 instance is part of the AMI itself.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/WindowsGuide/AMIs.html","title":"Amazon Machine Images (AMI) – Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"1dd2a814eff8bee8cf3e4da0ee6a245e","text":"Block device mapping","correct":true},{"id":"fb7756bd7b1e9872836772b73ccf9aac","text":"Launch permissions","correct":true},{"id":"6f8a7b69b94bd2a5b6d397b35bf7a403","text":"EC2 instance","correct":false},{"id":"11d5f5efdfcf29972a22321321560da7","text":"EBS snapshots or root volume template of an EC2 instance","correct":true}]},{"id":"el8zebxq-qo1d-az5o-l4lp-vmh132hnt1zd","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following Compliance guarantees attests to the fact that the AWS Platform has met the standard required for the secure storage of medical records in the US?","explanation":"A HIPAA certification attests to the fact that the AWS Platform has met the standard required for the secure storage of medical records in the US.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/pci-data-privacy-protection-hipaa-soc-fedramp-faqs/","title":"AWS Compliance"},{"url":"https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hippa_(disambiguation)","title":"HIPPA or HIPAA"}],"answers":[{"id":"827ec26130c30cc52e3fb178e0ef505c","text":"FERPA","correct":false},{"id":"dba5359496e7ea71f51ce4da1ee614bd","text":"GLBA","correct":false},{"id":"d0a785d52ac4a841f7efdf0098d9ebd5","text":"HIPAA","correct":true},{"id":"739f96badcfca6fd03c1e5b17971c9de","text":"HIPPO","correct":false},{"id":"393dceb94f2cac456fd53985a67d72b3","text":"HITECH","correct":false}]},{"id":"rku8juy8-m8eo-xhrd-ap7e-a3nhr9045k2l","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the below is TRUE when considering subnets in a VPC?","explanation":"By default, all subnets within a VPC can communicate with each other, without needing any other resources or configuration. NAT Gateway and Internet Gateway work in different scenarios to allow your subnet to communicate with the internet and are not required to communicate between subnets","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonVPC/latest/UserGuide/VPC_Subnets.html","title":"VPCs and Subnets"}],"answers":[{"id":"ecfdf4b74c36d8d497f1023a5b24e38f","text":"Subnets within a VPC can only communicate with each other if an Internet Gateway is deployed","correct":false},{"id":"8ff25f40e9a121e4620e1809190ac599","text":"By default, subnets within a VPC cannot communicate with each other","correct":false},{"id":"b5bcf23beb0bab6ed020ef6e8d9026ef","text":"Subnets within a VPC can only communicate with each other if a NAT Gateway is deployed","correct":false},{"id":"bdcce4ddcc3bbe6bca2d1851d91ff3a2","text":"By default, all subnets within a VPC can communicate with each other","correct":true}]},{"id":"6ffbb1ad-0c02-4ae3-82ba-fa79a62e733b","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following support pricing plans provide access to both the AWS Personal Health Dashboard and the AWS Health API?","explanation":"Having an AWS account grants you access to the Personal Health Dashboard to receive alerts and remediation guidance regarding events affecting the services underlying your resources. However, if you go with either the Business or Enterprise support plan, you will also get AWS Health API for integrating health data and notifications with your existing in-house and third-party IT management tools.","links":[{"url":"https://console.aws.amazon.com/support/plans/home?#/","title":"AWS Support Plans"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/health/latest/APIReference/Welcome.html","title":"What is AWS Health?"}],"answers":[{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true}]},{"id":"5fd1imv7-lqes-7e9n-vz33-eau71532v2ly","domain":"security","question":"How does AWS Shield Standard help protect your environment?","explanation":"AWS Shield Standard is included at no extra cost but will only block DDOS attacks on your AWS resources - it will not scan the contents of incoming or outgoing traffic (this is a function of WAF) and will not protect your environment from viruses","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/waf/latest/developerguide/shield-chapter.html","title":"AWS Shield"}],"answers":[{"id":"84009024e233c4995b00c514474f0ae5","text":"By Blocking DDOS attacks","correct":true},{"id":"55063c26653acc06bd00cc13e1acc3a4","text":"By scanning your instances for viruses","correct":false},{"id":"3e6fc5c29a49e9d5c54bd4950ad5cbe0","text":"By scanning outgoing application traffic for sensitive information","correct":false},{"id":"b1d6309ddb9cc2f856af5a3bab83f37e","text":"By scanning incoming application traffic for know attacks","correct":false}]},{"id":"9n50o6rz-03s4-bpbd-i7dy-36qby4h0ka5x","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are you responsible for when running an RDS database on AWS?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model for managed services, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance), as well as making sure the underlying OS and application is up to date. You as the user are responsible for keeping your data secure.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"57b862a3c428d3330f8c03216acd2c16","text":"Controlling access to the database","correct":true},{"id":"86da12905838c932b65844a3fa01aa08","text":"Updating the operating system","correct":false},{"id":"0266c79a8678f6881cc2857043b46509","text":"Controlling access to the network hardware","correct":false},{"id":"2b6b76aaf679124f3da7b20c5df23923","text":"Updating the database software","correct":false},{"id":"8782b4a6bdea28cea082df1413a7f818","text":"Controlling access to the compute hardware","correct":false}]},{"id":"aosxkeh9-qevj-zztz-qgkg-lo0glwr2ccoh","domain":"billing","question":"By default, when using consolidated billing, which of the below will the master paying account be able to do in the member account?","explanation":"By default, using Consolidated Billing only allows the master account to view the billing information from the member accounts - no access is automatically granted for users in the master account into the member accounts beyond this. ","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/consolidated-billing.html","title":"AWS Consolidated Billing"}],"answers":[{"id":"29f838d6149e7ff36b4692f879dbd0a3","text":"Grant access to member account to other users","correct":false},{"id":"3dbb078ea9c1eaf843d213ba217af3e8","text":"View billing information","correct":true},{"id":"25e6de5387e3157c014e2c6f2b0e810e","text":"Make changes to resources","correct":false},{"id":"54e29f93505b20fe2cc8af1cce96a33b","text":"View any data stored","correct":false}]},{"id":"rv438cbg-ow9h-jrfd-gxxt-a83ko2ojlo7c","domain":"concepts","question":"In AWS' Global Infrastructure, what are Edge Locations responsible for?","explanation":"Edge Locations host a Content Delivery Network called CloudFront.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"0df5575df91cfdc3471135f97cd57b5b","text":"Providing redundant backup to your AWS services","correct":false},{"id":"7e293752730d983b3fb263bc37525a5c","text":"Hosting a Content Delivery Network called CloudFront","correct":true},{"id":"e2dd2357c3f760b6df8cd9ef82402a0e","text":"Providing disaster recovery services","correct":false},{"id":"3d5bde6fd721f0872d6ad91a83e073cd","text":"Providing independent power grids to Availability Zones","correct":false}]},{"id":"5h2eems4-whow-d044-2cp2-g3qhkjhzcl4q","domain":"tech","question":"You need to host a file in a location that's publicly accessible from anywhere in the world. Which AWS service would meet that need at the lowest cost?","explanation":"With S3, objects can be accessed from anywhere in the world via a public URL. An RDS instance is used for hosting databases. An EBS Volume requires an EC2 instance to be accessible, and would be more expensive than using S3","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/s3/","title":"About S3"}],"answers":[{"id":"e2ab7c65b21ed8cc1c3b642b5e36429e","text":"S3","correct":true},{"id":"248c1b0bcb74394beb4a08030c4a6847","text":"EBS","correct":false},{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false},{"id":"0f41d6f36f8eaee87ea08d9f4b1159e2","text":"RDS","correct":false}]},{"id":"82a1ac91-eb42-41c9-b216-39000de68a5c","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following statements are true about who can use IAM roles?","explanation":"A role can be used by either an IAM user in the same AWS account as the role or a user in a different AWS account. A role can also be used by a web service that AWS offers; a prime example is Amazon EC2.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_roles_terms-and-concepts.html","title":"IAM Role Terms and Concepts"}],"answers":[{"id":"bf2d86ed19745c25bb11a0239b17b7a5","text":"An IAM user in a different AWS account than the role","correct":true},{"id":"85f661e32207f8f663f531db040bc97a","text":"A web service offered by AWS","correct":true},{"id":"df8acd03a312147855a4dbb0fc3cad51","text":"A web service offered by providers other than AWS","correct":false},{"id":"31124384faad90d323f0ac8b670e3d5f","text":"An IAM user in the same AWS account as the role","correct":true}]},{"id":"rqfj1uaw-51ci-mvl2-1djk-uzefaek5cehy","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following is correct?","explanation":"The number of Edge Locations is greater than the number of Availability Zones, which is greater than the number of Regions. Regions contain Availability Zones, therefore there will always be more AZs than Regions.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"07ebe9ccf5e5396c2f2c81de53d3829e","text":"# of Regions > # of Availability Zones > # of Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"916cfd186ad7a451ebd785b35c738429","text":"# of Edge Locations > # of Availability Zones > # of Regions","correct":true},{"id":"27268ba761c3ae0dbf9e4c8959f13e0f","text":"# of Availability Zones > # of Regions > # of Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"3782de3e5fc87f6e1a21193778c0d5bf","text":"# of Availability Zones > # of Edge Locations > # of Regions","correct":false}]},{"id":"d58bf9f4-44f6-49b5-b204-5aa9d88e98eb","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following is classified as an AWS Networking & Content Delivery service?","explanation":"API Gateway is the only service listed here classified as a Networking & Content Delivery service. It is used to create APIs to access AWS Cloud or other web services.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/","title":"AWS Documentation"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/apigateway/latest/developerguide/welcome.html","title":"What Is Amazon API Gateway?"}],"answers":[{"id":"58e3bfbabf904de43a6a22aca509b0d8","text":"CloudFormation","correct":false},{"id":"947642228a6d69446c74618fdde1bfd6","text":"Storage Gateway","correct":false},{"id":"ce1a41ee0352cee512475ef6a6233963","text":"Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2)","correct":false},{"id":"2ef9dd82927a3196ca2df3fc0cdf2e0b","text":"API Gateway","correct":true}]},{"id":"cliqnjyx-pd1z-74c0-p0h5-gl8ufv76fo42","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following are valid EC2 pricing options?","explanation":"On-Demand, where you pay for the resources you have used at the end of the billing period, and Reserved, were you commit to paying a certain amount every billing period for a length of time no matter if you used them or not, are the valid EC2 pricing options.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":false},{"id":"942d4e37dd5607ab68e54755540d4a47","text":"Reserved","correct":true},{"id":"e26ff95de7b422fa8d7999578d2becc3","text":"On-Demand","correct":true},{"id":"4cc6684df7b4a92b1dec6fce3264fac8","text":"Global","correct":false}]},{"id":"e9yzvx4u-z9ss-opgg-lwg4-h390rywj4hat","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following AWS services controls Authentication and Authorization within an AWS account?","explanation":"IAM (Identity and Access Management) controls Authentication and Authorization within an AWS account. Security Groups and Access Control Lists are tools within IAM that can help make that control easier to manage. AWS Shield is a separate service that helps protect resources from external attacks.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/iam/details/","title":"About IAM"}],"answers":[{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":false},{"id":"303a25c2935ec1fdb01208b6f4f65688","text":"Access Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"41dff7155cc7aeb11c06434f6a450bb3","text":"IAM","correct":true},{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":false}]},{"id":"8x0x6jdm-e0n1-0rb6-ibad-we2hbkuaxgvw","domain":"tech","question":"You need to store a collection of objects that can also be accessed from a different AWS Region. Which service should you use to do this?","explanation":"S3 allows you to access objects from anywhere in the world - as long as the appropriate permissions are set!","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/Welcome.html","title":"About S3"}],"answers":[{"id":"248c1b0bcb74394beb4a08030c4a6847","text":"EBS","correct":false},{"id":"e2ab7c65b21ed8cc1c3b642b5e36429e","text":"S3","correct":true},{"id":"e66f7962b812129e4a3890b1dab122c0","text":"Elastic Container Service","correct":false},{"id":"6ebb7423072c5943f52c11274fd71b0b","text":"DynamoDB","correct":false}]},{"id":"8ilibd7u-7ml9-492r-etu0-n4zubf409ykt","domain":"tech","question":"Amazon Lightsail is an example of which of the following?","explanation":"Lightsail is AWS' Platform-as-a-Service (PaaS) offering - this means that when using Lightsail you don't need to worry about all the components that are required to deliver the Instance such as storage, data, and instance size as AWS manages all that for you. Amazon Lightsail takes away many of the complexities of managing an Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS) solution, like some of the networking. This can also be a drawback, if you want to have a highly configurable service. Since Lightsail lets you run a variety of fully-features applications, it is neither a Software as a Service (SaaS), nor Function as a Service (FaaS) offering ","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/lightsail/","title":"About Lightsail"}],"answers":[{"id":"68c0c53c6a8ab47f4b611dbf1c347a26","text":"Software as a Service","correct":false},{"id":"0fdc9e547679a07630645143e79cce26","text":"Infrastructure as a Service","correct":false},{"id":"f53d5c67ce1a2058f77a32af9a7d0c66","text":"Functions as a Service","correct":false},{"id":"8f637a063500ec391f887ff70bda5f30","text":"Platform as a Service","correct":true}]},{"id":"wdqr2l66-jcd9-o6lx-b012-qodibilagwi2","domain":"tech","question":"You need to implement an automated service that will scan your AWS environment with the goal of both improving security and reducing costs. Which service should you use?","explanation":"An online resource to help you reduce cost, increase performance, and improve security by optimizing your AWS environment, Trusted Advisor provides real-time guidance to help you provision your resources following AWS best practices.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/trustedadvisor/","title":"About Trusted Advisor"}],"answers":[{"id":"92fbbd5478621cf8f70624389759b44c","text":"CloudTrail","correct":false},{"id":"739749e0ec278613ef4f8e6861efc722","text":"Trusted Advisor","correct":true},{"id":"9633b701743bf40ce928fb9fa4c0ed66","text":"Config Rules","correct":false},{"id":"0bcfa28115476b2bcfed146f27c465c4","text":"Service Catalog","correct":false}]},{"id":"768b0aa8-1fea-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Upon sign-up of an AWS account, how much Amazon S3 Standard storage will you get for no cost?","explanation":"When you sign up for an AWS account, you will get 5 GB of standard S3 storage for the first 12 months under the AWS Free Tier.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/free/?all-free-tier.sort-by=item.additionalFields.SortRank&all-free-tier.sort-order=asc","title":"AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"70f79b00cb7649d94d473895d6c540d2","text":"1 TB","correct":false},{"id":"074c2f1dacf9047766e7f8d5dce71060","text":"5 GB","correct":true},{"id":"0d642755e7f12f7563e3db33bd0c39cb","text":"1 GB","correct":false},{"id":"3a6d03856b824be771cdd922375d59db","text":"20 GB","correct":false},{"id":"b3dd42c7956751be5d38b5c0cb2e09c0","text":"5 TB","correct":false}]},{"id":"aabc59b3-b883-454e-8336-dac6f49eb7c3","domain":"security","question":"You are a Systems Administrator who has just started adding IAM users to your company’s AWS account. However, you worry that the users will not create passwords strong enough to prevent unauthorized access. What is the most reliable way to ensure that users are using strong passwords?","explanation":"Use Identity and Access Management (IAM) to apply an IAM password policy. While awareness and training are critical to developing good security practices, the most reliable option is to use an IAM Password Policy, which won't allow users to use lower strength passwords.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_credentials_passwords_account-policy.html?icmpid=docs_iam_console","title":"Setting an Account Password Policy for IAM Users"}],"answers":[{"id":"da197ad4fa2d98027feab02afd84d7fc","text":"Speak with each IAM user individually about the importance of creating strong passwords.","correct":false},{"id":"6cb5679faafdf0c247c2543bdca0e635","text":"Apply an IAM password policy to ensure users create appropriately strong passwords.","correct":true},{"id":"2ef38712519600d72d012e44a6dcb5a3","text":"Ask for the password of each user and create a much stronger one by yourself.","correct":false},{"id":"a08ccc3650b327c02cd13367d8ffa875","text":"Hold an AWS webinar to stress the importance of creating strong passwords.","correct":false}]},{"id":"hgb6veam-i287-99i8-3v3f-0sxjtcea43qf","domain":"tech","question":"How does S3 Transfer Acceleration help you get your data into S3 quicker?","explanation":"S3 Transfer Acceleration uses AWS' network of Edge Locations to ingest data, and then uses the most optimal path within its own network to reach S3. Although compression and splitting data up before upload can also help speed things up, these are not offered by transfer acceleration. AWS does not let you send in data on your own disks, and although Snowball does let you to send data in without going across the internet, it is only useful when working with massive amounts of data.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/transfer-acceleration.html","title":"Amazon S3 Transfer Acceleration"}],"answers":[{"id":"9e82d26d8d807aff3537debfbdbbfa3f","text":"By splitting up your data into smaller chunks and uploading it simultaneously, then putting it back together on S3","correct":false},{"id":"7152ecba5a6dedddfb04c7c1751a7fc1","text":"By compressing your data to make it smaller for upload, then de-compressing it onto S3","correct":false},{"id":"bded189801290994bc7203f5c28e9812","text":"By using AWS's network of Edge Locations to upload to a location closest to you before taking the most optimal path within AWS's network","correct":true},{"id":"25e2178eda752fbf1b65aca4d8e31d7e","text":"By letting you send the data in on a disk your provide (saving on upload times) then copying it to S3","correct":false}]},{"id":"yvxo9l3i-wh4o-2dqm-3mnu-snzqe8qbcn6w","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following best describes an AWS Region?","explanation":"A Region is a distinct location within a geographic area designed to provide high availability to a specific geography. Regions are a key concept in AWS' Global Infrastructure - each is made up of one or more isolated (within that region) Availability Zones. There are often multiple AWS Regions on each continent, such as North America","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"cd212d0c12772fef24104f0585e29933","text":"A collection of data centres that are spread evenly around a specific continent.","correct":false},{"id":"02994d9c387a384eeaa6efd09a6dd102","text":"A distinct location within a geographic area designed to provide high availability to a specific geography.","correct":true},{"id":"1230f90d0fb76db29194467e14f8e099","text":"A collection of databases that can only be accessed from a specific geographic region.","correct":false},{"id":"8c91beabafc69d771d60455febdc0927","text":"A console that gives you a quick, global picture of your cloud computing environment.","correct":false}]},{"id":"ltl6jev0-2f05-xevd-rnut-yi3l7ar7nzk1","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are principles of sound design when it comes to reliability?","explanation":"The elasticity of cloud computing means that you never need to over-provision or manage change at the resource level.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/what-is-cloud-computing/","title":"What is Cloud Computing?"}],"answers":[{"id":"2c081b2e4ef662d134361511c0f138e1","text":"Manage change at the individual resource level.","correct":false},{"id":"7f20528f07a394778f02e20e5453fc02","text":"When in doubt, over-provision.","correct":false},{"id":"c57c5e34d89769a30ca48ef1c1155033","text":"Scale horizontally.","correct":true},{"id":"25ddbfce9d53b8f5a9e09aad85948b96","text":"Stop guessing about your capacity requirements.","correct":true}]},{"id":"69916ab3-c78a-4abd-86a8-5dc73e90916a","domain":"tech","question":"Your manager approaches you this morning to tell you there has been a surprise audit announced by the internal audit team for all of your company's AWS Accounts. Which service would you use to provide the necessary information to the audit team?","explanation":"AWS CloudTrail is a service that enables governance, compliance, operational and risk auditing of your AWS account.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/cloudtrail/","title":"AWS CloudTrail"}],"answers":[{"id":"311bdda432aba736b8dcb987523c0c92","text":"CloudWatch","correct":false},{"id":"1aa2d5ab75afef6fa4ccd1e3b22174d4","text":"QuickSight","correct":false},{"id":"9deb03cd21d41a691cdc24bfaab2820c","text":"Inspector","correct":false},{"id":"92fbbd5478621cf8f70624389759b44c","text":"CloudTrail","correct":true}]},{"id":"nncwnx24-taau-zgsd-blel-newfprz6u93i","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are principles of sound design when it comes to security?","explanation":"The AWS Cloud includes many design patterns and architectural options that you can apply to a wide variety of use cases. Some key design principles of sound design when it comes to security include: Apply security to all layers, enable tracability, and implement the principal of least privlidge options.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/apn/the-5-pillars-of-the-aws-well-architected-framework/","title":"The 5 Pillars of the AWS Well-Architected Framework"}],"answers":[{"id":"4bb4d3eefe3829a2b20a099180702f9f","text":"Apply security at all layers.","correct":true},{"id":"ff94370d49b79e8817f49bbbc97dbf02","text":"Apply security to your application only.","correct":false},{"id":"718831eabf7a4582f906032cd06bcea7","text":"Implement the Principle of Least Privilege","correct":true},{"id":"d0f7903229df2e315b9c9561f18a4b7c","text":"Secure your physical resources.","correct":false},{"id":"214beb729ce64f08fe84798c5bbedd6f","text":"Enable traceability.","correct":true}]},{"id":"97909ec2-34ad-4743-b7cc-ca2c83c62cc1","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following statements are true of the AWS Free Tier?","explanation":"The AWS Free Tier offers some services for free for the first 12 months after signing up for an AWS account. It also offers free trials of select AWS services for a short period. So, usage is governed by these principles. Although there are some service usages that are always free, this does not apply to EC2 Micro instances nor S3 storage of up to 5 GB.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/free/","title":"AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"c90c4c865ee803cfa9bbe8e9a2d845c9","text":"Amazon S3 storage of up to 5 GB is always free.","correct":false},{"id":"f60585d833d73cf82fda96da1f19b3e6","text":"Some AWS services come with short-term free trial offers.","correct":true},{"id":"424553c7a1502a98737dfd15823ee215","text":"Some AWS services are free for the first 12 months following the initial sign-up date to AWS.","correct":true},{"id":"42c6d3d9032dba4f7aea8ddeedde2f6c","text":"You will never be charged for use of EC2 Micro instances.","correct":false}]},{"id":"c6jepoji-nqyo-0t96-juj8-ob2lymloevj9","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are components of the AWS Assurance Program?","explanation":"Certifications/Attestations and Compliance with Laws and Regulations are cornerstones of the of the AWS Assurance Program.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/pci-data-privacy-protection-hipaa-soc-fedramp-faqs/","title":"AWS Assurance"}],"answers":[{"id":"19d78b92947f957cca4c7698118fdb82","text":"Following industry best practices","correct":false},{"id":"fc0d934854b825185d4ea2079edf68c3","text":"Compliance with Laws and Regulations","correct":true},{"id":"de208db5a32df9befe2ed7f080863f9e","text":"Customer Testimonials","correct":false},{"id":"506afacef0a47cc7635b5cf0a3476c31","text":"Certifications/Attestations","correct":true},{"id":"4dc626268903b46b79d0a76e0a989cf8","text":"Partner Validations","correct":false}]},{"id":"c314b972-e56b-46d5-a876-4754ac7a336a","domain":"tech","question":"A Web Application Firewall operates at which layer of the OSI model?","explanation":"The seven layers of the OSI model in ascending order are Physical, Data, Network, Transport, Session, Presentation, Application. A Web Application Firewall protects web traffic from mallicious exploits and operates at the Application layer, Layer 7. Network-level protection, like that offered by AWS Shield, operates at Layer 4.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/waf/","title":"AWS WAF"}],"answers":[{"id":"537c230a6d35c80a253f85b1c6d607c4","text":"Layer 7","correct":true},{"id":"0d5a8f512ae075b876e8bb239d6be642","text":"Layer 2","correct":false},{"id":"73d19b475178ae97c94ed26431e3b138","text":"Layer 4","correct":false},{"id":"5ab5764b458bd4674dffe82c5f1cda53","text":"Layer 1","correct":false}]},{"id":"1azz6wyo-s13f-kikp-9zl7-obrtwc74xz52","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following AWS services should you use if you'd like to be notified when you have crossed a billing threshold?","explanation":"A CloudWatch alarm can be set to monitor spending on your AWS Account.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/cloudwatch/","title":"About CloudWatch"}],"answers":[{"id":"726f0166d9c5880f1646439cf8ed64d3","text":"AWS Cost Allocation","correct":false},{"id":"311bdda432aba736b8dcb987523c0c92","text":"CloudWatch","correct":true},{"id":"80550a5f8560e734862d7290c462206d","text":"AWS Budget","correct":false},{"id":"739749e0ec278613ef4f8e6861efc722","text":"Trusted Advisor","correct":false}]},{"id":"aaa7dqnz-f7nv-g9bl-zfw2-2xko23ptcj2t","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are you responsible for managing when storing data in S3?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model for managed services, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance). When it comes to S3, the customer is responsible for all aspects of the data being stored on S3, and who has access to manage the S3 service for that account","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"f661780dbe84a95f44f8622698e4b2a9","text":"Who has access to the S3 Infrastructure Software","correct":false},{"id":"ae48532652716e286fa0be350d5545e3","text":"Who has access to the storage hardware","correct":false},{"id":"6c507c7b28d852214aa62ba95c5c7009","text":"Who has access to data you stored on the S3 Service","correct":true},{"id":"2f6823eab5248af1500c3b8329fab352","text":"Who has access to the S3 Service","correct":true},{"id":"3278fa01d394d47605876669eaea2957","text":"Who has access to the network hardware","correct":false}]},{"id":"e915ef52-2be6-4fba-8d62-b668f639c29a","domain":"billing","question":"To stay within the AWS Free Tier using Amazon EC2 for the first 12 months of having an AWS account, which of the following instance types should you use?","explanation":"One of the EC2 requirements for staying within the AWS Free Tier is using EC2 micro instances only. While the other instance types can be cheap, only t2.micro is eligibile for free tier usage","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/free/?all-free-tier.sort-by=item.additionalFields.SortRank&all-free-tier.sort-order=asc","title":"AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"05c25e549fbb3f158f12a9945bff38ee","text":"t3.medium","correct":false},{"id":"ab61127647912c159c3fc08e9a102efc","text":"t2.small","correct":false},{"id":"1d4f2c610dbeb44e7ba09fed19564c76","text":"t2.micro","correct":true},{"id":"cc114cafeb511c9cbe6666312f54a8de","text":"m5.medium","correct":false}]},{"id":"8d9bfa67-4685-4ba8-a5a7-d0518daba638","domain":"billing","question":"If you want access to all AWS Trusted Advisor checks, which of these support plans will provide that?","explanation":"You must choose either the Business or Enterprise support plan to gain access to all AWS Trusted Advisor checks.","links":[{"url":"https://console.aws.amazon.com/support/plans/home?#/","title":"AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false}]},{"id":"bce6da84-1c95-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Upon which of these measurements is AWS Lambda pricing based?","explanation":"With AWS Lambda, you are charged based on the number of requests for your functions and the amount of time (duration) it takes for your code to execute.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/lambda/pricing/","title":"AWS Lambda Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"880a586b8b9c63efeba6c7f9afae7dc0","text":"Data transfer","correct":false},{"id":"a817cbcc67f9a1988581b7d71d401622","text":"Number of requests","correct":true},{"id":"4789f23283b3a61f858b641a1bef19a3","text":"Memory","correct":false},{"id":"e02d2ae03de9d493df2b6b2d2813d302","text":"Duration","correct":true}]},{"id":"8dmul9q1-wi30-bo4k-81j9-ztcv7dgeoybt","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following EC2 instance types will realize a savings over time in exchange for a contracted term-of-service?","explanation":"EC2 Reserved Instances offer significant discounts for a contracted term-of-service, of up to 75% off. On-Demand instances are charged equally per-hour, regardless of how long they're run for. Spot instances are cheaper than On-Demand instances, but aren't intended for long term use","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"bcc129e8d9496a05a331c903d4c5bcb0","text":"Reserved instances","correct":true},{"id":"2a80e91907ea76d424690185914b6eae","text":"On-demand instances","correct":false},{"id":"409aa157dda2d7faab6bf2938e322891","text":"Discount instances","correct":false},{"id":"991236e27b7cb98a2eeff8897b3e0bb4","text":"Spot instances","correct":false}]},{"id":"caa31392-2fbc-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following engines are classified as relational databases on AWS?","explanation":"Amazon Aurora, Microsoft SQL Server, and MariaDB are three types of RDS engines on AWS. By contrast, DynamoDB is Amazon’s nonrelational database solution.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/","title":"Amazon Relational Database Service (RDS)"}],"answers":[{"id":"7f9733e208088b1ce6df3d4be1765396","text":"MariaDB","correct":true},{"id":"69670a9d53817d1ec89e685997343ce2","text":"Amazon Aurora","correct":true},{"id":"78898e52fcbdc5337204a384f2456d4f","text":"Microsoft SQL Server","correct":true},{"id":"6ebb7423072c5943f52c11274fd71b0b","text":"DynamoDB","correct":false}]},{"id":"wfisjo0f-usp3-160k-im9l-di4ay4ny42e8","domain":"tech","question":"Which AWS service is specifically designed to assist you in processing large data sets?","explanation":"Elastic Map Reduce (EMR) is a service that makes it easy to process large amounts of data efficiently. Redshift is a data warehousing solution. ElastiCache is used for caching data in memory for high speed read-access. EC2 is a general purpose compute service for hosting virtual servers. Whilst you could run big data processing tasks on EC2, it will be easier on EMR, which has been designed specifically for this purpose","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/emr/","title":"About EMR"}],"answers":[{"id":"f52a9d91766886fb3a524dd06d1581cb","text":"Redshift","correct":false},{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false},{"id":"50848259480914860b338e7baf94c29a","text":"ElastiCache","correct":false},{"id":"be94b3c024501e2d7e9e64f4e0d18af9","text":"Elastic Map Reduce (EMR)","correct":true}]},{"id":"4uvrqex2-fb79-fccq-6ogx-umyvygaxn7fi","domain":"security","question":"You are using your corporate directory to grant your users access to AWS services. What is this called?","explanation":"Federated Access is when you use an external directory, such as your coroporate one, to grant users in that directory access to AWS resources. Role-based and User group are more used to definied which resources a user is able to access once they have access, not the method by which they gain that access. Multifactor Authentication Access is the concept of a user requiring 2 secrets to be able to access the resources - usually their password and a 1 time code provided by a device under their control (e.g. a mobile phone).","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/identity/federation/","title":"Identity Federation"}],"answers":[{"id":"0db642c28b60c6a51547c3da2262902b","text":"User Group Access","correct":false},{"id":"d3973accf5dd88240811572d5f2608eb","text":"Multifactor Authentication Access","correct":false},{"id":"00347e1d2de42be9910e334d04fe60dc","text":"Federated Access","correct":true},{"id":"acce53b09f08060687cd88c30bce9db8","text":"Role-based Access","correct":false}]},{"id":"5rgnown1-vlu1-k6s2-9cwf-bvemaocz7dod","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following is the document used to grant permissions to users, groups, and roles?","explanation":"A Policy is the document used to grant permissions to users, groups, and roles.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/access_policies.html","title":"IAM Policies"}],"answers":[{"id":"3e9adbb1694363232ef581246d090ea7","text":"Paradigm","correct":false},{"id":"888a77f5ac0748b6c8001822417df8b6","text":"Protocol","correct":false},{"id":"51359e8b51c63b87d50cb1bab73380e2","text":"Policy","correct":true},{"id":"88e23d388b9ab82cfa398a2fdb26467f","text":"Passbook","correct":false}]}]}}}}
